That's it. You're gonna take him, now, run!
It's broken!
Ah!
Oh! Come on!
The Knights'
score stands!
But... the injured player...
Looks like he
cannot continue.
looks like he
Let's hold for
a speeder recovery.
What are you doing?
That's roughing
the passer.
That's a 15-yard
penalty, you idiot!
Don't make me kick you
out of the game, coach.
This is my house, boy.
Can't run this field, boy.
Hey!
You motherfucker.
Hey, hey, listen to me.
Hey, are you blind?
Fix!
Coach, don't
question me.
If you want to
keep coaching,
get back to your
sideline now.
Yeah.
You son of a bitch!
How much you paying these refs?
Who cares.
Your only star
player is out.
You have no chance of winning this game today.